He say, "Good morning,"
and ask, "How is your hand?"
It's-- It's better.
What's left of it.
Sorry.
We would like to speak with you
if you feel well enough.
Yeah, that's all right.
- Coffee?
- No, thank you.
Tell us about this place you mention,
in Slovakia.
It's this... .
It's some kind of factory...
... where these people,
these very rich people...
... they pay to torture and kill kids.
Mostly backpackers.
And they killed two of my friends.
They take you from this hostel...
... and they bring you
to this factory and... .
I went there looking for Josh.
He was one of my friends
and they took him there and... .
And they... .
They killed him.
It was horrible.
He ask how you survive.
I... .
I escaped.
Who organize this place?
I don't know.
It's some kind of hunting club. They... .
They all have the same tattoo.
It's a dog.
It's a bloodhound dog.
Strange that you mention this tattoo.
Why?
Because someone was found dead
in a train station bathroom in Vienna...
...with this same bloodhound tattoo
you describe.
Security tapes from this station
show him entering from a platform...
...where a train arrive earlier that day
from Slovakia.
It came through
the same station in Vienna.
You were on that tape.
Did his tattoo look something like this?
What the fuck's going on?
Help! Somebody help me!
Jesus.
You hungry?
It's 3:15 in the morning.
I have to take these with food.
I wanna know if you want anything.
Yeah, I want you to talk to someone.
When are you gonna tell
Josh's mother what happened?
I'm not.
She still thinks her son's in Europe.
What the fuck
am I supposed to tell her?
- She'll go straight to the police.
- Yeah, exactly. Someone should.
No, no one should. You don't get it.
These people are tied into everyone.
Somebody starts asking questions...
...they're gonna come after me
and find me.
At my grandmother's house? I've
been coming here since I was a kid.
I can barely find the place.
I had to ask my sister for directions.
- You told your sister we were here?
- Yeah. So?
- Well, who else knows?
- No one!
Jesus.
I'm doing this for your protection too.
You know that, right?
Oh, Paxton... .
Look.
I took you back because I felt bad.
But you're going crazy.
You wake up every night screaming,
and I can't sleep.
Well, that won't
be a problem anymore.
Paxton, that's not what l--
Oh, fuck.
Morning!
Paxton?
Hey.
Lorna?
Sorry. I was trying to be
in the moment.
Absorb.
Do you think she ever saw a cock
before this class?
If she did, it was in a Botticelli.
Oh, my God.
If I hear her talk about how emotional
the Botticelllis are one more time...
...I swear to God,
I'm gonna choke the bitch to death.
Until Tuesday.
Are you all packed for Prague?
- Jeans. No heels.
- Awesome.
I can't do it on the cobblestone.
I don't know how you do it.
I can teach you if you bring heels.
Axelle.
Hands on your pencils, boys.
- Would he ever?
- Excuse me, girls.
- Excuse me. Hi.
- Hi.
- May I see?
- Oh, they're just rough.
Show her. Don't be shy.
That's the one of you.
- Oh, wow, that's beautiful.
- Thanks.
How much would you want for it?
I wouldn't sell them.
You can have this one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God, thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Can I buy you a drink or something?
Oh, I'm actually late. We're
catching a train to Prague, but... .
- I don't know. Maybe some other time.
- Okay.
- Yeah! Okay.
- I'll see you.
- All right. Bye. Thanks.
No, Dad. It's Prague.
We're gonna be fine.
It's not the Ukraine.
No.
No, Dad,
do not book the Four Seasons.
Book it, bitch. Book it. Please!
Because, Dad, no college students
are staying at the Four Seasons.
And, you know, it's for old people.
So thank you, but please don't.
What?
Yeah. Yes, we have chaperones.
Okay, love you. Bye.
Jesus, I hate that he calls
every fucking five minutes.
- All right, let's go.
- Hold on. We gotta wait for someone.
Who?
- Yeah.
- No.
She cornered me in the apartment.
She's homesick, crying.
I felt bad. What am I supposed to say?
She's homesick for Baltimore?
We're in Rome, for fuck's sake.
She's not that bad.
Wow, is that a new journal
you got there?
Yeah. It's a travel journal.
For emotional callbacks.
Of course.
Lorna, we're gonna grab a drink.
You wanna go?
I'm okay. Thank you.
All right.
Well, we'll see you in a little bit. Okay.
Knock yourself out, buddy.
See you later.
Excuse you. Asshole.
She's like a 20-year-old grandmother.
Whatever. She'll watch our stuff.
She's happy there.
That's what she likes to do.
Oh, we didn't order these.
They're from girl.
Whoa, your girlfriend's stalking us.
Hey. What are you doing?
You inspired me to take a trip.
Watch this.
You've got to be kidding me.
Hello. What's your name?
Do you know where we could score,
like, party favors?
What do you need?
I don't know.
Like, bud and ecstasy and, like... .
PCP?
Ice? Peyote? Crank?
Okay, okay, bud and X are good.
Sure.
We go back to my car. I got some.
Yeah?
- Yeah?
- Okay.
Fuck. You know what?
I'm trying but I can't find them.
Just hang on, yeah?
- You want drink?
- No, I'm fine.
Hey, you know what?
It's okay because we can just get
it at the club when we go to Prague.
No, stay.
I find them. Okay?
You smell nice.
- Whit, we gotta go. Lorna's waiting.
- Yeah, we have our friend.
- You have friend?
- Yeah.
One, two, three, perfetto. Otherwise,
we have to take turns, huh?
You know, we're gonna go,
so never mind.
Where you go? I knew you were
a tease, you fucking cunt.
What the fuck did you call me?
I called you
stupid fucking American cunt!
- Fuck you!
- You know what?
The train to fucking Prague
is long, you bitch.
We'll come see you.
Are you fucking insane?
What? I fucking hate that word.
"Oh, you stupid American cunt."
I fucking lost my temper.
Okay, but it's not like
we're on campus and you can...
...call the dean
and file a report or something.
Oh, my God. Lorna, what happened?
Some guy took my iPod.
What?
Is there, like, a police officer
on the train or something?
- Yeah. I'll go check.
- Okay.
It had everything.
That's awful. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
It's those fucking guys.
The fucking guys, the Italian guys
from the room down the hall.
- What do we do?
- Just be quiet.
- Hi.
Excuse me.
Did one of you girls lose this?
Oh, my God!
How did you know this was mine?
I saw some guy run out of your room.
He tried to take my bag.
I fought him off
and this felled out of his pocket.
I'm a little worried he might
come back looking for me.
Well, do you wanna come in here
and hang out with us?
- Really?
- Yeah, we have an extra seat.
- Yeah, come in.
- Totally.
Thank you.
I think...
...we all need a little of this.
Oh, awesome.
Oh, no, thanks. I don't drink.
Thank you.
As my father always says:
"Nazdrovia." To your health.
So are you going to Prague
for the football match?
I kind of wanna go home.
Oh, I don't blame you. I got
robbed twice on the overnight train.
There are so few safe places
left in Europe.
So where are you going?
On a little spa vacation.
Where?
Slovakia.
Wait, wasn't there, like,
some war in Slovakia?
There hasn't been war in Slovakia
for 50 years.
That's Bosnia, darling.
- Oh, like you knew.
- I did so.
What are the spas like there?
They're the best natural hot springs
in the world.
I go twice a year. It's great to get away
from the Italian guys.
They get to be a bit much.
Wow, hot springs?
That sounds so therapeutic.
I wanna go.
It's very easy. You just have to
switch trains in Prague.
It could be nice.
You know? I had enough gross guys
for one weekend.
Okay, we'll go.
Do you know of a good place to stay?
- Smart move with the shoes.
- What? It's so easy. You have to try it.
Hi. Can I help you?
- I need a room for my friends, please.
- Yeah, cool.
Your passports, please.
American. Good.
Yeah, cool. It's 10 Euros for night.
No. I got this one.
No. It's on me.
- Thank you.
- Money.
Thanks.
Here are your keys.
And this is a notice for
the harvest fair tonight, girls.
Will be sexy good times. Come on.
It's Dožinky. I know that.
They have it every year.
- Yeah.
- Lots of music, dancing, costumes.
Oh, my gosh! Could we go?
- It sounds kind of gay.
- Excuse me.
Oh, we are so going to
the harvest festival.
- Come on. This way.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Do you think they have any frescoes
in the room?
Wow, this room feels so timeless.
Are you kidding right now?
Oh, my God!
Sexy.
Come here.
Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about, huh?
Todd, what's up?
Yeah, nothing.
We're just finishing up breakfast.
Really?
Wow, I didn't think--
Jesus. You sure?
Yeah, yeah, okay. I can go right now.
I'll tell her I have to meet a client.
Okay.
See you.
No respect for me.
No respect for mother earth.
Well, don't you have
anything to say for yourself?
Well, that's just fine.
We can all ride home in silence.
Gosh! This village is so enchanting.
Lorna, are you having a
"journal-gasm" right now?
Actually, yes. Multiple ones.
I get to write about
how beautiful this village is...
...and I get to write about
what a raving bitch you are.
She comes back swinging!
- Well-played.
- Thank you.
Dollar!
Do you guys have a dollar?
- I got it.
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no. I got it. I got it.
Let me.
I have Smints.
Would you like a Smint?
Bitches!
Welcome to Slovakia.
You both have corner suites
with views of the river.
Here are your pagers.
Perfect. Thank you.
- You ready to do this?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
Really?
Because you look like
your dog just died.
I'm just jet-lagged, man.
I'll take a shower and I'll feel better.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Oh, my God!
Hey, guys!
Yes?
For the apartment.
Awesome, dude.
Those swords are like 1000 Euros.
Trust me, she can afford it.
Does she get, like,
a really big allowance?
No, it's more like an inheritance.
Her mom died when she was 12 and,
like, left her everything.
And so she keeps her dad
on an allowance.
- Really?
- Yeah.
She could pretty much buy Slovakia
if she wanted to.
Yeah. It's pretty rad.
Yeah!
Badass.
Let me see this motherfucker.
You're up, bro.
I think I'm gonna pass on the tattoo.
Come on, man, sit down.
A tattoo's not really me.
It's not my style.
I didn't know and I don't like needles.
I don't like needles very much.
Dude, what are you doing? Sit down.
Here's the problem. Linda. What
is she gonna say when she sees this?
My wife is not gonna
really understand.
Is there some other option?
Everyone must get tattooed.
Part of contract.
Yeah.
Let's do it. Come on, man.
Why don't you sit down?
These guys aren't playing.
A tattoo is
a little difficult to explain, Todd.
Didn't seem like you had
any problem explaining...
...the gonorrhea you brought back
from Thailand.
Can't believe you're bringing up
the gonorrhea. Every time--
Is there any problem here?
No, no. I just didn't know
that this was part of it.
Stuart.
This is not like going to a whorehouse.
You can't just back out.
Get in the fucking chair.
Yeah.
Come on, man. Look at this.
I'm fucking proud of mine.
Look what I found!
Okay, and before you say anything,
it's cider, it's non-alcoholic...
...and those little kids right there
made it.
- Oh, my gosh, really?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna go say thank you.
- Okay.
They don't speak much English.
This is quite possibly the most
alcoholic cider I've ever tasted.
Come on, it's good for her.
She needs it.
Thank you.
Well, cheers.
Oh, my God, my song! Let's go!
Come!
Come on, Borat.
Let's see what you got.
There they are.
Three o'clock.
- Jesus.
- Right?
It's fucking crazy, huh?
Dead ringer.
Happy fucking birthday, bro.
- Dude, where you going?
- In for a better look.
Me?
Hi.
Would you like to dance with me?
No, thank you. I'm--
I'm not nearly drunk enough.
Come on. I'll show you how.
No, really. It's easy.
No. Thank you, really, but my feet.
I'm tired.
I could have helped you.
Excuse me?
Hey.
That guy make you some troubles?
No. He's fine.
What he say to you?
Nothing. He just wanted to dance.
He won't bother you anymore.
Oh, he wasn't bothering me.
Here. Take a drink.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Oh, I'm so sorry!
- Don't worry about it.
I'm so, so sorry. I'm such an idiot.
No, it's all right.
- Here, let me get you a drink.
- No, you don't need to.
- No, I insist.
- No, no.
I insist.
Beth! Beth!
Beth! Oh, my God, Roman wants to
take me on a boat ride...
...and he's just so suave
and he's amazing...
...and he doesn't speak English,
but we understand each other.
Yeah. Just promise me you won't
go on a boat ride with him, okay?
Why not?
What's the big deal?
You don't fancy him?
Just because he's not "Whitney
approved" or "Beth approved" looking?
No, I'm not saying that at all. I just
want you to stay here where it's safe...
...we're all together,
we don't get separated.
Just promise me
you won't go on a boat ride with him.
Lorna, promise me
Beth. It's okay.
- Okay. You promise?
- Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Roman.
Okay, two, please.
- Here you go. I'm so sorry about that.
- It's okay.
- Cheers.
- Cheers. Thanks.
So, what brings you
to this corner of the world?
Her. Firestarter.
And you?
I honestly don't know.
I'm sorry, there's probably...
...a small army of Slovak boys
all fighting over you.
Why travel all this way
just to talk with an ugly American?
You're not that ugly.
Really?
Well, cheers to that.
Cheers.
Hey, your friend looks like
she's having fun.
Yeah.
I get to listen to them have sex later.
Can we switch?
I'm over at the Dvorzak hotel and...
...it's probably been three centuries
since anybody's had sex over there.
Oh, maybe your table's ready.
That's-- That's a long story.
Well, I'll have to hear about it
another time.
I'm gonna take off,
but it's a small village...
...l'm sure we'll meet again.
- I'm sure we will.
All right. Good night.
Good night, Beth.
Did I tell you my name?
No, no. I heard your friend use it.
But I forgot to tell you mine. I'm Stuart.
Good to meet you, Stuart.
Good night.
Lorna!
Lorna.
Excuse me.
Lorna!
Beth, I'm sorry!
You promised.
I know.
I'm sorry!
It's so peaceful.
It's so secluded.
Roman, what are you doing?
Come to me.
Close your eyes.
Roman! Roman!
- On a boat
and I have no idea where she is.
- How does she get back from that?
- Beth, come on!
Oh, fuck!
Beth!
I cannot leave her alone with this guy.
You know, you just go ahead
and I'll wait for Lorna.
- You go. Yeah.
- Yeah?
- All right. Thank you so much.
- Okay.
- Sure. Yeah.
- Thank you.
Fuck!
- Dude, are you coming?
- Are you okay?
I'm good. I'm good. No, I'm fine.
- Are you all right?
- Dude, I'm fine.
Have another cocktail.
All right, good night.
No, Whit. We're going to sleep.
- We are?
- Yeah.
Okay, is he hot,
or is he too, like, eastern bloc?
He's fine. But can we please go
get some rest? Come on.
Oh, you're so sweet. No, I'm fine.
It's okay. I'll take care of her.
I'm sure you will, but not tonight,
all right? Good night, Miroslav.
Good night, Miroslav!
I'm sorry. He was just so shady.
Whatever. I wanted to fuck him, but... .
I know you did. I'll make it up to you.
I guess Mr. Rabbit's gonna have to
go down the hole again tonight.
Do you have a AA?
Mr. Rabbit!
Come here, Rabbit!
Do you remember the first guy
in your high school to get laid?
No, but I remember the last.
Well, I do. This kid Greg.
He came back from summer break,
something about him had changed.
It wasn't anything he said or did, but
something was different. You knew it.
I know what you mean. It's like you can
sense it the way an animal senses it.
Exactly. Like an animal.
Sometimes you meet a guy and there's
something fucking scary about him...
...something that makes you think,
"This guy has killed somebody."
He doesn't have to act tough.
He never has to say it.
But like an animal, you can sense it.
You know that this guy's got the balls
to do what few others can.
And that's you after today, my friend.
People are gonna fucking fear you.
Linda is gonna fucking fear you.
What we do today is gonna pay off
every day for the rest of our lives.
- Where's your pager?
- It's back in the room.
- Come on. What the fuck?
- I just figured you had yours.
Is it me? Because it feels like
you're, like, having second thoughts.
You've never really been into this.
I feel like I'm talking you into it.
I don't wanna be doing something
and keep talking about it--
- It's different from taking on an image.
- I am so fucking tired of talking about it.
It's time we fucking do it.
To the next level.
To the next level. No, wait.
Isn't it bad luck to toast with water?
Yeah. Bad luck
for whoever meets us today.
Yeah. Let the games begin.
Hard, hard, hard.
Hey.
- Hey, did she call?
- No. I just checked.
I love that Lorna's the only one of us
that got any action last night.
- Hey, I tried.
- Keep trying.
Yeah, she'd say
this place is majestic.
Sure.
I bet she's making him
breakfast right now.
No, I bet she's in a cum coma.
Thank God.
At least she has something
to write about in her journal.
Please! Please!
Please! Stop!
No!
Stop! Please! Please!
Please! Please!
Please, no!
Relax.
Come up here.
Whit?
Axelle?
Fuck.
Whit!
Guys!
Axelle! Whit!
Stop. Please help me!
- Go away.
- Please help me!
- Just go away from me!
- No, no, no.
Help me.
These men are chasing me. Please.
I tried to help, but you don't listen.
Go away!
Dollar, bitch!
Stop!
Get in.
Yeah.
The police will be here soon.
They are looking for your friends.
Thank-- Thank you.
More tea?
Please.
Thank you.
So, you and Sasha...
...are you two...?
- Oh, no. God, no.
He's old enough to be my dad.
What does he do?
He does auctions.
Come. Let's get you some clothes.
No!
Help! No! No!
What did I do wrong?
Please don't hurt me.
Please don't hurt me. I'm sorry.
I not hurt you.
Okay. It's okay.
I clean you up.
Please, please help me.
You have a bruise.
What is that?
What are you doing?
I make you pretty.
Pretty for what?
For the client.
Client? What client?
Give me. No.
No.
We do...
...nails.
No!
No! No!
Oh, my God.
No!
I'm worried about Whit.
Whitney seems like a tough girl.
She'll be okay.
You have a scratch.
Yeah.
- It's sore.
- I'm sorry.
You have such beautiful skin.
Thank you.
Who's that?
Just some friends.
Come. You should lie down.
I'll wake you up when the police arrive.
Do you think we're sick?
Fuck, no.
Dude, you look anywhere in the world
where there's no law...
...whether it's fucking Chad
or New Orleans...
...and this is the shit
people are doing, bro.
We're the normal ones.
Any idea what
you're gonna do in there?
You don't even wanna know.
Jesus.
They're listening. They're listening.
Beth, it's me. It's Stuart.
From the fair.
Don't talk loud. Okay?
If they hear us talking like this...
...they're gonna fucking kill us both.
You hear me?
I need to know you're listening.
Okay?
What the fuck are you doing?
What is this place?
Where the fuck are we?
Stuart!
Remember when I said that
I didn't know what I was doing here?
Well...
...this is what I'm doing here.
What is this place?
This place... .
People come here... .
People come here to kill people.
What? Who kills?
Oh, my God, are they gonna kill us?
Well...
...not...
...us.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Are you gonna kill me?
- You're gonna kill me!
- No. No, no! No, no, no.
No. Jesus, no. No.
Then what the fuck
are you doing here?
What the fuck are you wearing?
Someone brought me here...
...the same as you.
Someone I know.
Look...
...he wanted me to--
To do this with him.
What?
Stuart, please.
Please just let me go.
Help me get out of this chair.
Please. Please help me get out of this
chair. Get me out of this chair, please!
You probably used that face to get
whatever the fuck you wanted.
Fucking skank.
Oh, that's fucking rich.
You should see your fucking face.
- We gotta get out of here.
- We can't.
They think you're gonna kill me?
You're not some monster.
- I'm not that guy.
- No.
No, I know.
- I know you're a good person.
- I'm not that guy.
I know. Of course not.
I'm not that guy.
- Okay. Okay.
- I'm not that guy.
We're gonna get out of here.
I'm not that guy.
There must be a co--
Oh, fuck. Fuck.
Christ! Fuck!
God!
Fuck!
Don't you have family?
Don't you have a wife?
My wife?
I'm not allowed to kill my wife.
- Finish?
- Yeah, I'm finished, all right.
Hey, hey! You cannot done.
You go in room, finish.
You know what? I am fucking done.
If you don't like it, you can go in
and finish her yourself.
You cannot leave unless
you complete. It's contract.
I fucking paid!
You have my money
and you can keep it!
I am not going back in that room!
I'm done!
Hey! Hey!
Hello. Special offer.
But she's only available
for the next 20 minutes.
Do you want her?
We'll let you know.
Six-fifty.
Yes?
Apologies for interrupting you, but
we have special available right now.
Very good price.
Where's Todd?
Problem with friend.
May I borrow this
for a moment, please?
What do you think?
Should I do it?
I mean, I wouldn't pay
more than a grand for her...
...in this kind of shape, but... .
I mean, look at that.
She's not gonna last that long, huh?
You should see
what she did to my friend.
I'll take her.
A souvenir from your friend.
Notice anything different about me?
I bet you fucking do.
Fucking bitch.
Fucking respect me now.
I don't fucking work for you!
I don't work all fucking day
for you to humiliate me.
To tell me I'm shit.
Never fuck me.
Look at you.
What?
What, you got something to say?
Do you? You do, bitch?
Yeah? Oh, good.
Well, it better be fucking good.
- Let's fucking hear it. What?
- I'm not your wife.
I'm not your wife, Stuart.
I'm not your wife.
She doesn't understand you.
She doesn't understand you like I do.
- And I see how you're strong.
- I am strong.
- I am fucking Hercules!
- I see.
I know. I know. I see it. I see it.
I saw it last night.
I was hoping you would kiss me.
I wanted you to kiss me.
I thought about you all night.
Get on the fucking floor.
Are you scared?
You fucking better be.
I am.
I like it.
Look at me.
Bitch.
You fucking whore.
Get in the chair!
Get in the fucking chair!
Fucker!
What's the code?
Fuck you!
What's the fucking code?
- Your birthday.
- What?
What is your birthday?
December 12th.
Oh, that is fucking sick.
What the fuck? It's not opening.
It's not fucking opening!
Oh, yes, it is.
Do it! She's right up there
behind you! Kill her!
Motherfucker! Shoot her!
Kill her! Kill her!
Don't shoot!
Be careful, for God's sakes!
She'll cut! She'll fucking cut!
Don't shoot!
Fucking she'll cut! She'll cut!
Get Sasha!
You gotta do it! I'm the fucking
customer here! Do it, for fuck's sake.
Jesus fucking Christ. Oh, shit!
- Sasha!
- Get him!
- Wait! I wanna buy my way out of here.
- Wait!
- You can't afford it.
- Don't tell me what I can't afford.
There's nothing I can't afford. I could
buy and sell everyone in this room.
You going to call your parents
for money?
No, motherfucker, it's my money.
Just get me a PDA, a SWIFT number
and a recipient name.
I have accounts in Switzerland,
Luxembourg and the Isle of Man.
Just name your fucking price!
Trust me, I got it.
Okay.
We negotiate.
- This is bullshit!
- This is business.
I'll pay more!
Not with a second mortgage
on your house...
...and your daughter's
private-school tuition.
That's why your friend pay.
What's the number?
Money is not the only issue.
We have contract here.
What kind of contract?
Anyone who come to this place...
...cannot leave...
...without killing.
They're still gonna kill you,
you fucking stupid cunt.
What did you say to me?
You're a stupid fucking cu--!
Let him bleed to death.
Misha, no!
Isn't this great?
Hey, get back here!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Hey!
You fucking shit! Wait!
Bitches!